A short description of mapper of reducer for Homework: 1
---------------------------------------------------------
Md. Yasin Kabir, e-mail: mkdv6@mst.edu	
Ayan Roy, e-mail: ar3g3@mst.edu	
Archana Patkar, e-mail: appgqb@mst.edu


===>
In this program we have used the following algorithm for the Mapper Function:
► Step 1: Reading the data from the .txt file.
► Step-2: Reading each of the line in the file individually using mapper.
► Step-3: Dividing each of the line in the file into corresponding tokens using StringTokenizer. 
► Step-4: All tokens except English Alphabets and white space, has been replaced with empty strings.  
► Step-5: Transform the each words to lowercase so that starting or capitalize words also match. 
► Step-6: We use Capital "CHAPTER", to detect the words in each chapter. When ever we encounter that words we defined it as a new chapter. We didn't count the words which apears before chapter 1.
► Step-7: We added an information using a integer number with the words to keep track from which chapter that word is.


The following algorithm has been implemented for the Reducer Function:
► Step- 1: The reducer recive the key value pair for each word. The reducer receives the input from the mapper in the form of <Word10, 1> 
where word10 is a example words which denotes it from chapter 1. Later we substring those words and subtract the value from 11 to get exact chapter number. 
► Step-2: We take summation of word occurances in different lines for every occurances. 
► Step-3: We use a HashMap to store the value of each words.
► Step-4: We invoked the void run() function so that we can easily modify the calling of context.write and use it only at the last iteration of reducer.
► Step-5: An array of HashMap used to store all the words separately for individual chapter.
► Step-6: We consider a word and check the number of occurance of that word in each chapter. If a word appreas more than 5 in every chapter we calculate its total
occurance and print it. However, due to our very large list of stop words we only able to get a few. For that reason, we consider the words which appears in all the chapter for at least once and write another output file. 
► Step-7: Finally, we print the count of all words sparately for each chapter. 

In the mapper and recuer files which are attached we tried to add as much as comment possible for clarifying our intentions. 

